

Brandon Lozano

Front End Web Developer



Self-Driven, with 2 years of experience gaining and retaining clients in a variety of projects including custom websites, logo design, and photography. Proficient in developing responsive, modern, and functioning websites - deploying them on my self-managed server using Git. Striving to grow in front-end design and develop more complex web applications.

CONTACT

email@brandonlozano.com

210 687 4371

brandonlozano.com

San Antonio, TX

SKILLS

5 HTML5

SASS

∃ CSS3

⇔ Ubuntu Server

Apache Web Server

Git

Ps Adobe Photoshop

Ai Adobe Illustrator

INTERESTS

O Photography

🟂 Snowboarding

🖺 Hiking

X DIY Projects

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Freelance

07/2020 - Current San Antonio, TX

■ Developed a handful of responsive websites for clients accross industries using HTML, SASS, Javascript, Git, Ubuntu Server and Apache Web Server.

- Worked on all project aspects (written content, website design and developemnet, deployment and icon creation/image sourcing) in collaboration with clients.
- Maintained websites with change requests, server updates/management and ongoing website optimization to better load times and increase SEO rankings.

Graphic Designer

Freelance

07/2020 - Current San Antonio, TX

□ Created logos and product labels for self-sourced clients - projects were completed with client collaboration to achieve a look that best appeals to their target audience.

■ Edited projects based on clients needs and medium (web, social, and print).

Project Manager

Host It Solutions

07/2017 - Current

San Antonio, TX

- Manage client meetings to determine scope of work, time lines, 3rd party integration needs and go-live dates.
- Worked with in-house engineers to assign IP ranges for client projects, firewall allowances and interface with additional resources needed such as database and email servers. Scripted tools to deploy user credentials via SMS.
- Worked with clients to streamline their current workflow processes. Introduced programming features to automate manual procedures greatly reducing manpower and developing remote access tools to push data back to home office.

EDUCATION

High School DiplomaSmithson Valley High School

2013-2017

Spring Branch, TX